Do you think you two could stop snarling at each other every time you meet?
She's the one who's always glaring at me, rude!
Because you need to appreciate fried tofu fritters!
I suppose if you've been trying to kill each other since the moment you've met,
then there's nothing I can do.
Huh? No, I wouldn't say we always wanted to kill each other, right?
Yeah, I agree. That part came much later.
Okay, enlighten me.
Thank you.
I heard there might be a civil war soon
Looks like it
The royal succession dispute is finally coming to a head
At this rate, the neighboring country is going to capitalize on it
Humans are such foolish creatures
Every time they open their mouths, it's about conflict
They don't even try to enjoy their worthless lives
The priestess of the Holy Seas is here
Wait, the priestess?
What a miracle for her to finally come to our town
Thank goodness, she's come to save us at last
The priestess of the Holy Seas
She intervenes in human conflicts
And creates favorable resolutions
If the conflict is over water or food
She creates lakes and abundant harvests
If humans clash, she uses her power to make them lose their will to fight
She must be a god
Or a similar type of entity at least
Either way, it's against the rules for such beings to interfere in human society
That must be her
What's she like?
That woman?
She's neither a god nor a divine messenger
Is she...
Does she think this is a joke?
What are you doing?
Honestly, a dragon-turned priestess?
And they believe you?
I could ask you the very same thing
Why is the Emperor of Demise's daughter living amongst humans?
If I remember correctly, you're called Toru, right?
And if you must know, I don't believe human beings should be fighting each other
It is foolish to sacrifice unnecessary blood
I have the power to stop that, so I do
Are you saying there are Harmony Dragons that exist who will actually do some work?
I bet you've had quite a few human sacrifices offered up
It doesn't matter, I don't need human sacrifices
You don't?
Why not?
Who would ever want to eat a human?
I don't believe they're tasty
I'm willing to bet there are much more delicious things in this world
And it is my belief that humans will be the ones to create them
I see
She's the oddball Quetzalcoatl mentioned
You must be Elma, then?
Nice
What food do you usually exchange?
Are you absolutely sure you don't belong to the Chaos faction?
Speaking of oddballs, you're not exactly typical either
I've never met a Chaos dragon who wasn't looking for chaos
None are ever willing to engage in conversation
Well, before I eliminated you, I wanted to do some investigating
Investigating? Huh
Would you care to join me for a while and further your education?
Where?
Here in the world of humans
We can investigate together
So you two traveled together for a while, then?
Yeah, I guess
I put up with her self-righteous act for too long
I truly don't know what I was thinking, Kobayashi
Sounds to me like you were both just feeling each other out
Trying way too hard to get along
When you had very different values
Yeah, I guess that sounds about right
I was more interested in getting to know Elma personally
She had so much freedom and always seemed to be doing exactly what she wanted
I know it's been a while, but that's the way I remember it
Mm-hmm
Okay, so then what?
Oh, right, sorry
We came to understand one another somehow
We accepted that we'll never agree
That's why it made sense
To kill each other
Hmm
That makes no sense at all
Why, Toru?
What possessed you to destroy the palace?
Don't you understand that was supposed to be a symbol of peace?
Was it?
The thought of peace requiring your presence gave me chills
What?
This palace was erected for you
A place for people to come and worship you as a god
And from this origin, a religion centered around you took root and adopted a class-based society full of inequality
In time, there would come to be conflict with those who refused to accept you
I would have forbidden that!
You're not listening to what I'm trying to share with you
Tell me, do you intend to remain here with these humans for all eternity?
Granting the desires of others, and acting as a symbol of worship forever?
I'm dying to know if you intended to let yourself get dragged into the human agenda
Or did you foolishly believe you were operating under your own power?
You diverged from your plan, Elma
I'm disappointed in you
I can't stand how disgraceful you've become
I've no choice but to kill you and wake those humans from their dream
If that's what you want
Then come for me, Toru!
Take my life!
I knew this was coming
It was never going in a good direction
But what else was I supposed to do?
They brought me food as compensation
I couldn't resist, and it was delicious!
I'm not going to be able to do it
She's...
She's so, so strong!
And that was it
That was how we severed ties conclusively
Hmm...
That sounds simultaneously grandiose and petty
And in the end, I returned to the Harmony Faction's base
And I guess that was that
I never got involved with humans again
So you fight now because you two get along so well
What do you mean?
Did you not listen to our story?
No, we don't get along!
We're completely at odds with each other!
I couldn't tell
Toru's been uncharacteristically chill
And you always seem to have your hands too full
With work to try to lead humanity
So, wouldn't that mean you don't really have a reason to fight in this world?
What?
Come on, Ms. Kobayashi
Do you not understand why things are like that here?
What?
It's because the food here is irresistible
And both Toru and I have a gluttonous streak
I'll never be anything like you!
What do you mean?
You're way too easily enticed by food!
I'm not!
Please, tasting human culture is the best way to understand humans!
You'll make up any excuse to stop your stupid face!
As if you're not totally booked on human food yourself
Day after day, you're cooking
They've become so close, they understand each other's thoughts
Then they fight to shave away the parts they still can't accept
Trying to compare it to your unnatural appearance
I've always wanted to have friends like that myself
I don't even know what natural means!
You don't know what natural means!
Things are like that.
非常的 status
There's always reasons why individuals eat the chicken
To be honest human beings
We look at the 안ie
To be honest human being
The reason why they say??
Love you to Alaska
I'm going to kill you, E-Lulu.
All you do around here is sleep!
You need to go out there and get a job!
I promise I've been thinking about my future.
One more century...
You're not on Dragon Time anymore!
Oh, that's right, I forgot.
I'll help you with your work for now.
You take that back!
As if you could ever handle the work of a maid!
Do not underestimate me or I'll be forced to prove you wrong!
Isn't that what Kobayashi is always saying to you?
Wait, this work you speak of.
Does Kobayashi do that?
Yes, she does.
And now she works harder so that you can eat too.
Then I guess I can work.
I want to work with Kobayashi's place, though.
I'll erase your existence!
You're scaring me. Please stop!
And I'll melt her, Mom!
What does Emma have to do with this?
If you're trying to preserve your laziness,
there are ways you can search for a job without leaving our house.
Use the computer.
No, thanks.
I'd rather go out and test the jobs myself.
Shall we go look around?
It's my first time passing through here.
I've flown over to the roof several times, though.
You're kind of like a cat.
Are you sure you wouldn't be better off living in the wild?
Oh, fine.
I should admit you have been putting in some effort.
You learned perception blocking, which is challenging.
And you managed to form proper hands, which I appreciate.
You've worked very hard.
I kind of like when you're nice to me.
I like you.
You shouldn't get so personal.
Fine.
I still like Kobayashi more.
You would.
Nothing yet?
I can't believe you haven't seen anything you'd want to try.
I can't do anything with meat and fish without wanting to devour them.
Spoken like a true chaos dragon.
Flowers make me want to trample them.
It's true.
We were born to destroy.
Books make me want to burn them.
Classic chaos dragon trait.
Unfortunately, all those things are forbidden.
Yeah, I know.
It's so hard having to ignore those instincts, though.
On the flip side, we wouldn't be here if we weren't able to deny them.
You know how to do that?
Of course I do.
But, um, I guess that means there's nowhere here you can work.
Hey!
Let's play!
Okay, let's play!
Do you want to come with us?
Where are you going?
Shopping!
Yeah, sure!
Let's go this way.
Yes!
Yoo-hoo!
Hi, Kana!
Hi, Saikawa!
Oh, you're here!
Hi, Lady Toru.
Hi, Elulu.
Yeah, hi!
What are you guys doing here?
That's what I want to know.
Kana?
This is just where we hang out sometimes.
Are these ladies friends of yours, Kana?
They seem very pretty and nice.
My name's Toru.
This is Elulu.
We were searching for a part-time job for her, but...
Which one should we get?
Who cares?
They all taste great.
Yes!
Kana, this would look so good on you!
Try this one, Saikawa.
I have a yellow one.
I haven't seen you here before.
Are you the maid's little sister?
Wow, you have such an adorable shop, Miss Saida.
Elulu, this is Miss Saida.
Miss Saida, this is Elulu.
We see each other at the neighborhood association meetings.
Oh, no!
What happened to your poor leg?
I messed it up while jogging this morning.
I'm getting old, so I've been thinking of closing up shop one of these days.
No!
But as you can see, I don't think I can.
There are a lot of kids here.
Because we're a dogashi shop, many different children have been coming here for decades now
to get their favorite treat.
Could I work at the shop with you?
I don't know.
How old are you?
She's the same age as I am.
The same as you?
Let's see.
I'm not sure what to do.
I was thinking my grandson would run the shop after me.
But it might be better to have someone enthusiastic about it instead of someone reluctant.
I would recommend her.
Huh?
Oh!
Okay.
Wow.
You're working part-time at a dogashi shop?
It's the Obero shop.
Have you heard of it, Kobayashi?
That's the one at the end of the shopping district, isn't it?
She's forgetting to tell you that she only got hired because I lent her my voice of authority.
It's true.
She was firm when commanding her emotions, and I thought she was terrifying.
I need more praise, please.
I don't know that that was praise.
Will it be okay, the job?
You're worried?
You chose it because you're interested in it, right?
Mm-hmm.
When I started my job, I didn't think much about it until much later either.
Eventually, you'll discover things you find fulfilling about it.
I became a maid because I was interested in it, and it's very fulfilling.
So why aren't you betting me?
Elu, make sure you always respect the needs of others and do everything to the best of your ability.
This mage should not be considered a role model.
Rude!
Mizzcomo-yachi!
how-by-
I
Hm? What's wrong, Take?
I feel bad for my grandma. She hurt her leg.
Are you stuck helping out?
No. Apparently she hired someone,
but she wants me to go by and train them for her.
Wow. I'm impressed she agreed to hire someone outside the family.
Yeah. She asked me to bring a uniform over today.
But check it out. It's huge.
I mean, it looks big enough to fit an adult man.
So it bothers you that she hired a guy? That's weird.
I don't know where she could have met this dude.
He better not be some psychopath.
That's Granny's little warrior.
Shut up.
This is weird. What the heck are they like?
Good afternoon.
That's why it's an adult size. Crazy.
Are you Ida's grandson?
I'm Takito, yeah.
I'm Alulu. I'm 16.
That's what I'm supposed to say.
The same age. Your name. Are you a transfer student?
How did you meet my grandma?
I met her here when I asked if I could work for her, and then she hired me.
She didn't even think it over?
This is suspicious.
She's got to have some ulterior motive for wanting to work here so urgently.
So, how can I help you today?
Oh, right.
This is yours. A uniform and apron.
Things to wear?
Fun!
Cut it out!
What's wrong with you, you perv?
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
You naughty boy.
If you're sorry, keep your shirt on!
You're all changing in the back.
Oh, right. I understand.
What the heck was that?
Is she from a country with that kind of culture?
I don't want to go there.
Hey, Takito?
Just Take's fine.
What's the matter?
I can't get the buttons on top to close.
It's fine. You're fine. No one will notice.
Oh, I get it.
You're a pervert, huh?
What'd you call me?
You're staring.
No, I'm not. They're in the way.
I'll be in back.
Let me know if there's anything you don't understand.
She's a whole new breed of weirdo.
I'm surprised Grandma decided to hire such a bizarre person.
She makes less sense than someone with ulterior motives,
and it's scary.
Does she even know what she's doing?
Can I have this, please?
Sure thing.
I want that.
This one?
Yeah.
Do we sell these individually or as a set?
We sell them both ways.
Man, she's actually trying to do a good job.
And she does more than I would have.
I guess that's why Grandma decided to hire her.
How come you have such big watermelons?
Harassed on the first day?
How will she handle it?
These are actually called flame sacks.
They're so strong they can hold fire.
Whoa, that's cool.
What kind of deflection was that?
Do they hurt your back?
Are they heavy?
Would you like to hold them?
Stop! What are you doing?
Don't be weirdo!
Ah!
Poor Take, are you okay?
I'm sorry!
Uh-huh.
It's okay, bad boy.
What's with the delayed reactions?
Bye-bye.
Goodbye!
You two have a good night!
Want to know something?
I like kids.
They're fun to play with.
Hmm?
But I'm not allowed to play with them while I'm working.
I thought if I worked somewhere where there were children, it would be more fun.
It's time for us to close up shop for the night.
Maybe we could play together.
I'll show you how to spin a top if you want.
It's actually pretty easy.
Oh, yeah, that!
I'm dying to learn!
I'll go get it!
She's a nice girl.
Looks like I won't have to worry about Grandma.
Hey, Take.
I think I like you.
Who's that supposed to say that?
After Kobayashi.
And who's that?
Kobo what?
Here it is.
Watch closely.
Want to hear something interesting?
Apparently, humans make wishes on stars.
Did you know that?
Huh?
They pray to the stars for peace and happiness.
Or bountiful harvests, or health for themselves, their friends and families.
Sounds like they don't care.
Who grants their wishes, as long as they're fulfilled.
What an utterly inferior species.
And what would you wish for, Toru?
If your wish was guaranteed to come true?
Nothing, really.
I'd make a wish.
Oh, I'm sure you would.
All the yummy sweets in the world, that right?
You do know me quite well.
You're close.
But no, that's not it.
What then?
I'm going to have all the delicious food, and then I'm going to have your share, too.
Oh.
As you wish.
Our lunch break is way too short.
Don't you agree, Ms. Kobayashi?
Not really, no.
There are five places on my current list
that I really want to try for lunch,
but I only have enough time to hit two of them.
Most people only go to one.
I'm hungry, okay?
This week on Who's Rotten?
Capricorn.